https://safpar.com/privacy-policy/

Our Policy for Protecting Your Online PrivacyThis website uses Google Analytics to help Analyse how users use the site. The tool uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the webiste and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Safari Par Excellence.We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.You may choose to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically default to accept them, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.User’s Personal Information:Visitors to our website are able to make a purchase of our activities and/or accommodation and upload/download information. When you purchase through our website, you will provide personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number, credit/debit card details and other relevant information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for your purchase. This information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary, including: To fulfill your requests, to protect ourselves from liability, where we are required to do so by law. We will not use any of your personal information provided to us via a purchase to send you unsolicited emails. Any emails you receive from us will be with regards to your purchase and will include confirmations and itineraries.Should you sign up to our newsletter and provide us with your email address and name, we will not use this information for any other purpose than to send you periodic updates, offers and latest news. We will not sell or divulge this information to any 3rd parties.3rd Party PoliciesRelated services and offerings linked to or from this website have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Since we do not have control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend you review their policies before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with them.Contact Us+260 213 320606 - 08 (landline)+260 968 320606 (cell)zaminfo@safpar.comThe Explorer Club Group PagesThe Explorer ClubSafari Par ExcellenceThe Elephant CafeThe Victoria Falls WaterfrontInternational Student Identity
Adrenaline Hunter© 2020 SAFPAR.
All rights reserved.
HomeActivitiesWhite Water RaftingIntroductionDay TripsRiver Board Combo2 Day 1 Night Trips3.5 Day 3 Night trips5 Night Zambezi Experience8 Night Ultimate ExperienceOur GuidesFAQ’sThe Elephant CafeRiver CruisesCanoeing SafariZambezi River SafariZambezi Raft FloatGame DrivesVictoria Falls TourLivingstone Cultural ToursOther ActivitiesGeneral & WildlifeVictoria Falls ActivitiesWater-basedLivingstone Adrenaline ActivitiesCultureLower Zambezi Canoeing SafarisPackages8 Night Ultimate Experience5 Night Zambezi ExperienceLodgesVictoria Falls WaterfrontThe David Livingstone Safari Lodge & SpaThe River ClubRafting Festival2020Rates2020GroupsAboutZambiaLivingstone TownPrivacy PolicyBlogContact Us Sign up for our newsletterIncludes special offers, latest news and regular updates.
Full Name (required) Your Email (required) Please leave this field empty.Enter the characters below Safpar will not sell or pass on your details to any 3rd party.
